Juliana Nocchi Dobal

🖂 junocchi@gmail.com 📞 074 8474 4640 📍 London/Cambridge 👤 LinkedIn 🎯 GitHub

I am a Makers graduate Software Engineer with a background in Animation and HR. With my mentoring experience from teaching and working as Chief of Staff, I now enjoy mentoring people starting their tech journey at Codebar. I am a positive, methodical and highly organised person who values continuous learning. I am also passionate about building strong relationships and believe that collaboration, communication, and respect are essential for any successful project. For highlights of my professional skills from peers and managers, please have a look at my LinkedIn Recommendations.

Projects	Description	Tech
Solved (Treasure hunting App)	A live-action treasure-hunting App with clues to help the user to search for five secret London landmarks.	Node.js, Express, MongoDB Atlas, React Native, Expo Go and Jest. API calls to 2 different services and image recognition.
Acebook-Air (Website)	This social media platform allows users to create profiles with a picture, share and like posts, and update their personal details.	MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, and Cypress.
Pensano (Website)	I've developed this website with my peer group to showcase our work both collectively, as Pensano Devs and our individual projects.	JavaScript, React, Jest, and GitHub.

Professional Experience

EMEA Chief of Staff & Office Manager (Jun 2021 - Aug 2022)

VTEX - Ecommerce Platform, London - UK

- Managed day-to-day functions in 6 offices, the HR platform (~90 employees) and the purchasing flow; working closely with the Procurement, Legal, Finance and Controllership teams
- Mentored new Office Managers and Chief of Staff globally
- · Worked closely with senior management to develop and implement policies, create and maintain a strong organisational culture, attract and retain talented employees, and ensure that the company remained compliant with relevant laws and regulations
- · Contacted speakers and hosted weekly training for the Sales Enablement team, including Sales & Merchandising, Finance & Accounting, Supply Chain & Operations, Technology & Data, Digital Marketing

Senior HR Generalist & Immigration Adviser (Feb 2015 - May 2021)

Brazilian Naval Commission in Europe (BNCE) - Brazilian Navy Procurement Office, London - UK

- Primary contact for all UK visa enquiries (~300 processes, including family members)
- Developed strategies and policies to address conflicts and improve workplace relationships
- Managed all aspects of onboarding and offboarding, and the HR management system ~80 employees
- Awarded Best Employee for consistently producing high-quality work (Jun-Dec 2018)

Education & Languages

English: Full professional proficiency • **Portuguese**: Native proficiency

Full-Stack Software Development Bootcamp (Nov 2022 - Mar 2023)

Makers Academy, London - UK

- Awarded a full scholarship with Codebar & Makers Represent Scholarship Programme
- Self-led learning 16-week full-time training
- Designed and built 17 programs working with minimum prior knowledge
- Collaborated in Agile teams with a focus on XP values and pair programming
- Practised OOD, TDD and Git workflow, to ensure our code was robust, maintainable, and efficient
- Specific training in empathy, feedback and teamwork
- Tech skills: C#, HTML, CSS, Ruby, JavaScript, React, React Native, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Expo Go, Mobile iOS, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Jest, Cypress, Git and GitHub

Universidade Federal Fluminense, Niterói - BR

• Mediator of the "Digital Media and The Environment" session at the International Conference on the Arts and Humanities, 27-30/06/2013, Perugia - IT

Post Graduation in Animation (Feb 2006 - Dec 2006) - Distinction

Pontifical Catholic University, Rio de Janeiro - BR

- 3DS Max, Adobe Flash, Adobe After Effects
- Produced a short <u>stop-motion animation video</u> with the support of the Brazilian Government and in cooperation with the Film & Video Workshop (London)

BFA - Bachelor of Fine Arts, Design and Visual Communications (Mar 2002 - Dec 2005) - Distinction

Federal University of Rio de Janeiro, Rio de Janeiro - BR

• Teaching assistant of the Textile Workshop, from Mar-Dec 2005

Interests

- Regular attendee of <u>Creative Mornings</u>, the world's largest face-to-face creative community
- Volunteer coach at Codebar, programming workshops for underrepresented groups in tech
- · Other interests: Functional Nutrition & Watercolour Painting